亞利桑那州  坦佩市
許可證
Lisence?
-除蟲員  -是的
- Exterminator, huh? - Yeah.
三氟化硼  二氯甲烷
Boron trifluoride? Methylene chloride?
很危險的東西
Pretty serious stuff.
你是要去殺什么蟲子
What are you trying to kill anyway?
他們讓我殺什么我就殺什么
Whatever they tell me to.
加利福尼亞州  舊金山
中度烘培干卡布奇諾  加一份半濃縮咖啡
Medium cappuccino, dry, one and a half shots.
別加兩份
Not two.
-名字  -哈諾  J-A-N-O
- Name?  - Jano -- J-A-N-O.
訂單
輸入顧客姓名  哈諾
安東
Anton?
中度烘培干卡布奇諾
Medium cappuccino, dry,
一份半濃縮咖啡  安東
one and a half shots.  Anton?
安東
Anton?
這是你的嗎
This yours?
你為什么叫我這個名字
Why you call me this name?
電腦上顯示的是安東
The computer says it's for Anton.
喂
Hello.
在你的卡布奇諾涼掉之前趕緊喝了吧  安東
Take your cappuccino before it gets cold, Anton.
你是誰
Who is this?
知道你真實身份的某個人
Someone who knows who you really are.
我剛給你發了一個地址
I just texted you an address.
你有三十分鐘時間趕到那
You have 30 minutes to get there.
否則  我就把車臣的人
Otherwise, I introduce the Chechens
介紹給你的新任老婆和孩子
to your new wife and baby boy.
你要的東西都在后面
It's all in the back, everything you asked for.
三氟化硼  二氯甲烷
照我之前說的去做
Do what I told you to do.
好了嗎
Okay?
沒我什么事了吧
So I'm done here, all right?
想想你的孩子  安東
Think of your child, Anton.
我只要按一個鍵
With one keystroke,
就能讓一群兇暴的軍人去弄死你兒子
I can unleash an army of beasts to descend on him.
美國網站司令部
弗吉尼亞州 天使崖
已經九點五十八了
It's 9:58.
你說十點就不折騰我的腦子了
You said I could have my brain back by 10:00.
還有兩分鐘呢
Well, that gives us two minutes.
芯片位于組蛋白脫乙酰酶中
The chip is situated in HDAC 5.
它是管理情感的核基因
That's the genetic nucleus that regulates emotion.
我們要確定那里沒有異常
We have to be sure that there are no anomalies.
你最近有什么情緒波動嗎
Have you been experiencing any mood swings lately?
陣發性哭喊
Crying fits?
陣發性哭喊  沒有
Crying fits? No.
你的扁桃體情況可跟你說的不同
Your amygdala is telling me a whole different story.
加布里爾  你在這里什么都可以說
Gabriel...You know you're safe in here.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
-我們不會評論你的  -已經十點了
- We're not judging. - Guess what. It's 10:00.
別急  等一下
Come on, now, wait.
坐好了  派力奧
Sit it down there, Palio.
我們現在做的都是很重要的工作
This is serious stuff we're doing here.
你的情感很重要  很關鍵
Your emotions are important. They're critical.
實際上  你仍然在每天
In fact, you are still incorporating the chip
適應這個芯片
a little bit more every day.
它雖然不斷讓你變得強大
And while it will continue to make you more powerful,
但我們要保證你還是本來的你
we must be certain that you remain you.
什么意思
What do you mean?
這個芯片能勝過你的生理能力
The chip will always exceed your human abilities.
但不能讓它勝過你的人性
We can never let it exceed your humanity.
先生們  有情況了  10分鐘后去指揮室
We've got a situation, gentlemen. C-doc in 10.
你們也聽見命令了
You heard her.
不  不  等一下  等一下
No, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
電線  有電線
Wires. The wires. Wires.
左邊的那個人是文森特·卡內洛
The man on the left is Vincent Canello,
機密
證人保護資料
以前給塞巴斯蒂亞尼犯罪家族運貨的
a bag man for the Sebastiani crime family
后來指證了他們  被列入了證人保護計劃
put into witness protection after testifying against them.
鳳凰城的法警說
U.S. Marshal's office in Phoenix
他三天前從他們的監視中消失了
says he went off their grid three days ago.
右邊的那個是安東·拉迪克  車臣的化學家
Man on the right is Anton Radic, a Chechen chemist.
拉迪克在揭發他們之前為破壞營
Radic cooked sarin for the sabotage battalion
制造了沙林毒氣
before giving them up.
也被列入了證人保護計劃
Also in witness protection.
你們在想他們有什么共同之處
You're wondering what they have in common.
老故事了
Ah, it's the old
"黑手黨運貨的和車臣化學家進了一家酒吧"
"Mafia bag man and Chechen chemist walk into a bar."?
而這個車臣的化學家  我馬上閉嘴  抱歉
The Chechen chemist -- I am gonna stop talking now. Sorry.
一天之前  這兩個人都互不認識
Until 24 hours ago, these two men didn't know each other,
而現在他們在一起工作
and now they're working together.
-這怎么可能  -問得好
- How's that possible? - Good question.
卡內洛在保護計劃里的身份是注冊除蟲員
Canello's cover in witsec was as a licensed exterminator.
真不諷刺
No irony there.
他的許可證可以讓他買到許多
The license allowed him to purchase a number
受限制的化學藥劑
of restricted chemical agents,
而前天他在亞利桑那坦佩市買了這些藥劑
which he did in Tempe, Arizona, day before yesterday.
200加侖二氯甲烷[常用作溶劑]
200 gallons of methylene chloride,
90磅河豚毒素[強力神經毒素]
90 pounds of tetrodotoxin.
適當混合后
With the right compounding,
他能用這些藥劑摧毀一座城市
he could devastate a city with these agents.
他們兩人中一個負責買這些東西
One of them can buy the stuff.
另一個負責使用
The other one knows what to do with it.
那么  是誰把這兩人聚集在一起的
So, who put these two together?
一定是一個
Would have to be somebody who
能接觸到證人保護數據庫的人
had access to the witness protection database.
-是內部人員所為嗎  -司法部說不是
- An inside job? - D.O.J. says no.
系統被從外界入侵了
The system was infiltrated from the outside.
哇  你是說
Whoa, whoa, whoa, you're talking
司法部門最機密的數據庫
about the most sensitive database in law enforcement.
被人如忍者一般悄悄地入侵了
And that would take some serious ninja hack-fu.
看來出現了一個騎手
We've got a rider out there,
-我們需要找到他  -騎手是什么
and we have to find him. Who? A rider?
胡蘿卜加大棒策略由四個基本元素構成
Every stick-and-carrot op has four basic elements --
主謀[騎手]  受迫者[騾子]
The rider, a mule,
懲罰[大棒]  獎勵[胡蘿卜]
a stick, and a carrot.
入侵證人保護數據庫的是主謀
The rider that got into the witsec database
他通常有一大批穩定的受迫者
has a huge stable of mules.
-通常也就是那些罪犯  -懲罰是什么
Mostly criminals themselves. And what's the stick?
將你暴露給你曾做過不利證明的人
Exposure to the people they testified against.
那獎勵呢
What about the carrot?
保護你愛的人不受威脅
The most powerful leverage there is -- the opportunity
這也是最有效的獎勵手段
to protect the people you love from a credible threat.
伙計們  我們得快點找到這個人
Folks, we need to find this guy quickly.
二氯甲烷  磷酸鹽  河豚毒素
Methylene chloride, phosphate, tetrodotoxin.
二氯甲烷  化合物
河豚毒素  化合物
磷酸鹽  化合物
這些化學品都有半衰期  很快就會衰變
These chemicals have a half-life. They degrade quickly.
如果那個人是前天買的這些東西
If they were purchased the day before yesterday,
那在它們失效之前他還有48個小時
he'll have 48 hours before they're useless.
看來我們要去亞利桑那州了
Looks like we're going to Arizona.
去舊金山
San francisco.
你是怎么知道的
How do you know that?
這輛貨車有條形碼
The van has a bar code.
我查看了密西西比州西部的所有橋和隧道
I've chipped every tunnel and bridge west of the Mississippi.
那輛貨車今早經過了金門大橋
That van crossed the Golden Gate Bridge this morning.
卡西迪  詹姆森  尼爾森
Cassidy, Jameson, Nelson,
你們解決那個黑客
you're on the hacker.
加布里爾  萊利以及我  去舊金山
Gabriel, Riley and I are going to San Francisco.
一個小時后出發
Wheels up in an hour.
莉莉安也要一起去嗎
Lillian's coming?
她女兒住在舊金山
Her daughter lives in San Francisco.
加布里爾·沃恩
Gabriel Vaughn
美國網戰司令部特工
三角洲一級作戰部隊
YYeTs人人影視
┌
┐
└
┘
■
┌
┐
└
┘
本字幕由
人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作
任何商業盈利行為
我國戰功最卓著的士兵之一
One of our nation's most decorated soldiers.
他是位英雄
He's a hero,
┌
┐
└
┘
■
┌
┐
└
┘
翻譯
Michael
七七
木淺薰
衛老哥
章魚埃克斯
寶寶
而現在他是我們最秘密的武器
and now our country's most secret weapon.
加布里爾擁有一種極其罕見的突變基因
Gabriel possesses a rare genetic mutation
┌
┐
└
┘
■
┌
┐
└
┘
翻譯
CS小明漫畫家
早先森
Silence
時間軸
小式
密思恩
基因匹配
使我們能夠在他的大腦里植入微芯片
That allowed us to implant a microchip in his brain.
我們將他的大腦直接與信息網絡聯通
We connected his mind directly to the information grid.
互聯網
電話
衛  星
┌
┐
└
┘
■
┌
┐
└
┘
這是人類可望而不可及的
It's something the chip does that nobody expected.
校對
油炸電風扇
Michael
衛老哥
我可以在腦中重現事發時的虛擬場景
I can create a virtual snapshot of an event in my mind
┌
┐
└
┘
■
┌
┐
└
┘
特效
8T
并穿行其中
and then walk through it.
就像是虛擬的證據墻一樣
It's like a virtual evidence wall.
后期
寶寶
在美國網戰司令部
At U.S. Cyber Command,
我們為他組建了一支特別小隊
We created a highly specialized unit around him...
莉莉安·斯特蘭德
美國網戰司令部主任
衛星就位倒數  五
Satellite in five.
并安排了一名特工保護他
...and assigned an agent to protect him.
萊利·尼爾
美國網戰司令部特工
前特勤局探員
┌
┐
└
┘
■
他們有槍
Gun!
┌
┐
└
┘
總監
紫玉
他是第一個擁有
He's the first of his kind --
下一代智能的人
The next evolution of intelligence.
智能緝兇
第一季 第十集
好吧  你怎么了
Okay, what's wrong?
沒什么
Nothing.
加布里爾  要飛五小時呢  別逼我猜
Gabriel, it's a five-hour flight. Don't make me guess.
她坐在了我的座位上
She's sitting in my seat.
我覺得你應該用手提包占個座
Well, I guess you should have saved your seat with your purse.
這是一種儀式  萊利  類似巫術
It's a ritual, Riley -- like mojo.
就像連勝時不要換襪子一樣
Like not changing your socks when you're on a winning streak.
我希望你今天換襪子了
Please tell me you've changed your socks today.
指揮室有話對我們說
C-doc has something for us.
說吧
Go ahead.
我們瀏覽了證人保護系統的日志文件
We've gone over the witsec system log files,
我們能肯定
And we've been able to confirm
入侵行為是在國內
the hack originated domestically.
我們還為神經毒素
We've also run several computer models
建立了電腦模型
on the neurotoxin itself,
做出了一些特定的假設
making certain assumptions based on
基于盛行風的速度  濕度  霧氣等
prevailing wind speed, humidity, smog --
盡可能多的因素
As many factors as the model allows.
甚至包括了我們認為他們能合成的毒氣量
Including the amount of toxin we believe can be synthesized.
-也就是12至15公斤  -然后呢
We're thinking 12 to 15 kilograms. And?
情況不容樂觀
It's not good news.
你看到的是對最好的和最壞的情況的分析
What you're looking at are best- and worst-case analyses.
可能傷亡人數是多少
Casualties?
舊金山長約46.3英里[74公里]
Well, San Francisco's land mass is roughly 46.3 miles.
總人口基數...將近一百萬
Total population base -- just under a million.
-不過有件事情很奇怪  -怎么奇怪了
There is something weird, though. Weird?
根據這些化學藥劑  我們認為
Based on the chemical agent, we don't think
接觸毒物并不致死
exposure to the toxin will result in death.
那會怎樣
What, then?
組織壞死  肌肉麻痹  失去行動能力
Muscle necrosis, paralysis, total loss of movement.
受害人只有知覺  但不能行動
It would leave its victims all brain, and no body.
要是襲擊發生在鬧市區呢
What if the attack was to happen downtown?
那就是最壞狀況
Downtown would be worst-case scenario.
莉莉安
Lillian?
我聽到了
I heard you.
我知道你很擔心麗貝卡
I know you're worried about Rebecca,
但她不會有事的
but she's gonna be fine.
你的芯片很厲害  加布里爾
You can do a lot of things with your chip, Gabriel,
但你也沒法預見未來
but even you can't predict the future.
你給她打電話了嗎
Have you called her?
協議存在是有原因的
Protocol exists for a reason.
安全帶也一樣  但也有無效的時候
So do seat belts. Don't always work, though.
我保護女兒最好的方法
The best way for me to protect my daughter
就是保證這起襲擊不發生
is to make sure that this attack never happens.
因為一旦我們
Because the minute that any of us
因私廢公
put our own interests ahead of our job, that's the minute
才真是將我女兒的性命置于險境
that my daughter's life really is in jeopardy.
你可以回你自己的座位了
Oh, and you can have your seat back now.
我已經按你說的做了
I've done what you asked!
結束了  東西是你的了
It's finished. You have the product.
聽到了嗎
Do you hear?
我不干了  就這樣吧
I'm done! I'm finished with this!
你還有件東西要送
You still have a delivery to make.
歡迎來到指揮室移動司令部
Welcome to C-doc mobile command.
另一個家
Home away from home.
詹姆森
Jameson.
主謀還沒消息
Nothing on the rider yet,
-但是受迫者有進展  -稍等
- but we've got something on the mules. - All right, hang on.
中士  請把指揮室錄像調出來
Sergeant, can you put C-doc up on the monitor?
好了  請繼續
Okay. Go ahead.
制造神經毒素需要很高的溫度
Cooking a neurotoxin would require an extremely high heat,
還需要一個特殊的
demanding a very specific
直流式排氣系統來支持損耗
vertical-flow-hood exhaust system for the waste.
高溫和排氣就是關鍵點
Right, heat and ventilation -- they were the keys.
這個電力負荷是相當高的
We're talking about a relatively large load of electricity,
而且需要一個
electricity that would have to run
特殊的適當變壓器
through its own transformers.
還要與排氣系統匹配
Same with the ventilation system.
這樣的排氣量不是一個煙囪可以解決的
You can't vent that kind of waste product through a chimney.
那就從商用地產下手
So we began to look at commercial properties,
從那些可以隱藏這樣規模的制造的地方下手
businesses where this kind of production could be disguised.
干洗店  工業面包店  舊式燃料煉油廠之類
Dry cleaners, industrial bakeries, old fuel refineries.
我們調出衛星圖像
Now, we looked at satellite imagery
找到了14個符合描述的目標
and pulled up 14 targets fitting our profile.
地理位置偏僻
All of them are isolated,
熱信號很高
very specific heat signatures,
而且  電能消耗很高
And, boom, spiked power draws.
-好的  -好
- Nice. - Okay.
聯通服務器  開始搜索目標
Funnel your intel here so we can set up the searches.
與此同時  我還要給
In the meantime, I've got a briefing
當地警力和救災人員做作戰指示
with local police and disaster crews.
要是他們找到了實驗室
If they find the lab,
監督搜索的任務就交給你倆了
I want you two overseeing the search.
收到
Copy that.
你很擔心她
You're worried about her.
她不對勁
She's not herself.
那位女人可不是靠她
That woman not only worked her way out
父親的名聲爬上來的
from underneath her father's shadow.
她在我這個年齡時
But by the time she was my age,
已經是陸軍情報中心指揮官了
she was already the head of army intelligence,
更不要說網戰司令部都是她一手創建的
Not to mention she practically invented cybercom.
你偷偷調查過人家
Snooping around personnel files?
不需要調查
I don't have to.
情報中心的每個女人都
Every woman in the intelligence community
把莉莉安當偶像的
wants to be Lillian.
反正我是沒見過她公私不分
Yeah, well, I've never seen her let it get personal.
你是說從來沒有表現的像你一樣嗎
Are you saying you've never seen her act like you?
真的假的啊
Seriously?
我說了  我不需要雜志
I told you -- I don't want any more magazines.
-媽  -你好
- Mom? - Hi.
天哪  嗨
Oh, my god. Hi.
雜志怎么了
What's this about magazines?
沒什么
Ah, it's nothing.
只是不停的有推銷員上門
It's just the salesman keeps coming by.
隨便給陌生人
Well, it's probably not a good idea
開門可不好
to open your door to strangers.
最好讓雷克來應付推銷員
Maybe Rick could deal with the salesman.
他已經不住這了
Rick's not here.
他找到工作了嗎
Did he find a job?
他找到了個新女友
He found another girlfriend.
我沒事  都分了好幾個月了
I'm fine. It's been months already.
這幅真棒
This is very nice.
畫的什么
What is it?
是一個因為孩子死去而哭泣的天使
It's an angel weeping over the death of a child.
開玩笑的  媽媽
I'm kidding, mom.
我才開始畫  我都不知道畫的是什么呢
I just started it. I don't know what it is.
那么  你為什么會來舊金山
So...what brings you to San Francisco?
業務
Business.
拯救世界嗎
Saving the world?
你父親怎么樣
How's your father?
你可以自己打電話問他
You could call him and ask him.
看看你的頭發  都這么長了
Look at your hair. It's gotten so long.
-真討厭  -不  真美
- Oh, it's horrible. - No, it's beautiful.
你真美
You're beautiful.
這是怎么了
What's going on?
沒什么
Nothing.
-媽媽  -你能一天都待在家嗎
- Mom. - So are you gonna be home all day?
為什么
Why?
因為那個
That's why.
只是  要處理一點
Just...kind of in the middle of --
處理一點事情
The middle of something.
是我
Yes.
尼爾森是對的  我們找到了實驗室
Nelson was right. We found the lab.
毒品呢
What about the toxin?
沒發現
Negative.
我們在一家老油漆商店里
We're in an old commercial paint shop,
很難找到具體結果
so it's hard to get a solid result,
但這里絕對有人在制毒
but there was definitely a cook here.
不過產品都不見了
The product's gone, though.
盡快把殘留物標本交給卡西迪
Get all residue specimens to Cassidy as soon as possible.
我想知道我們要處理的是什么濃度水平
I want to know the concentration levels we're dealing with.
麗貝卡  我要離開一下
Rebecca, I need to leave for a while.
我們以后再談好嗎
Could we talk later?
媽媽  我還有四幅畫要畫完  所以
Mom, I have four paintings to finish, so, you know,
我希望我能早點知道你要過來
I wish that I'd known you were coming by earlier.
-可我不知道  所以  -親愛的
- But I didn't, so... - Please, honey.
我真的很喜歡跟你聊天
I'd really like to talk to you.
好吧  媽媽  沒事的
Okay, mom. Fine.
-待會兒給我打電話  -好
- Call me later. - Okay.
再見
Bye.
你說這地方一年前就破產了嗎
You said this place went belly up a year ago?
據我所知是這樣
As far as I know.
那為什么還有監控攝像頭在工作
Then why is there a working security camera?
-有人監視了他們嗎  -是正在監視
- Someone was watching them? - Is watching.
正在工作中
Feed's live.
我的耳塞  有人打電話來了
My earbud -- someone's calling.
來電
網絡電話追蹤
來自一個網絡電話號碼
It's coming from a VOIP number --
就是通過互聯網協議的語音電話
Voice Over Internet Protocol.
跟那個攝像頭是同一線路
It's on the same line as that camera.
那你接啊
So answer it.
你的設備不少嘛
That's some equipment you have.
竟然能打通我的電話  刮目相看
Pulled my number out of the air -- impressive.
我試圖對你進行面部識別
I tried facial recognition on you,
但你好像并不存在
and you don't seem to exist.
所以才會給我打電話嗎
So you thought you'd call me?
你知道人們關于好奇心是怎么說的吧
You know what they say about curiosity.
只有被逮住的貓才會被害死
Oh, the only cat that gets killed is the one who is found.
看來我有麻煩了  你發現了我
Guess I'm in trouble. You found me.
不能這么說
Not quite yet.
你的朋友萊利·尼爾  她看來是存在的
Your friend there, Riley Neal -- she seems to exist.
直到近日之前  她都是特勤處的
Secret Service agent, although until only recently,
然后她也突然消失了
At which point she, too, vanishes.
你是誰
Who are you?
你先說
You first.
加布里爾
Gabriel?
他看見的我也能看見  別的監控也在啟用
I can see what he sees, the other monitor feeds,
但是通路不停變化  我無法定位他
but the trace is bouncing. I can't locate him.
那不是你唯一的攝像頭  對嗎
That's not your only camera, is it?
你不只是在觀察我們  你在觀察一切
You're not just watching us. You're watching everything.
你走路的樣子像個運動員  游泳的嗎
You walk like an athlete. Swimmer?
然后軍隊就把你弄去了嗎
Then the military got ahold you?
你打算給我建個檔案嗎
You trying to work a profile on me?
只是閑聊而已
Just making small talk.
你呼吸很吃力  你受傷了嗎
Your breathing's labored. Are you injured?
你的追蹤連邊都沒挨著
Your trace didn't even come close.
我們一會兒再談
We'll speak again soon.
雞蛋玉米卷餅
Taco scramble!
這里真黑啊
So dark in here.
我們讓太陽照進來一點
Let's let a little of the day in.
雞蛋玉米卷餅
Taco scramble, huh?
看起來像玉米卷餅  但是有雞蛋
It's like a taco, but with eggs.
-股市怎么樣  -蕭條
- How's the stock market? - Sluggish.
我覺得我自己能行
I think I can do it.
-好吧  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
真好吃
It's good.
真高興
Oh. I'm so glad.
如果你確定自己沒問題  那我就去買點東西
If you're sure you're okay, I'll go get groceries.
好的  沒問題
Oh, absolutely.
好了  再見  親愛的
Okay. Bye, honey.
再見
Bye-bye.
加布里爾跟他說話了嗎
Gabriel spoke to him?
這個主謀想辦法搞到了他的手機號
Our rider managed to pull down his cell number.
你們的手機都加密了
Your phones are encrypted.
他黑進了證人保護項目  亞當  他很厲害
He broke into witsec, Adam, he's very good.
如果他不是個兇手  我都想把他收進麾下了
If he weren't a murderer, I'd hire him.
能不能回溯通話  追蹤他
Any chance to repeat this call, trace it?
他會打回來的
He'll call back.
先聯系對方的人會迫切想再次聯系
The ones who make contact can't wait to talk again.
我還是希望你在總部坐鎮
I want you back at Angel's Bluff.
-為什么  -你是部門主管
- Why? - You're the head of the agency.
像這種連加布里爾都沒辦法的危機
In the event that Gabriel can't stop this,
我可不想讓你前排看戲
I don't want you in theater.
多謝關心  但我要和我的人共進退
I appreciate your concern, but I'm staying with my people.
莉莉安  我知道你女兒住在那邊
Lillian, I know your daughter lives there.
我勸你是因為你我是朋友
I'm speaking to you as a friend.
那你就不該質疑我的客觀性
A friend wouldn't question my objectivity.
油漆行的檢測結果顯示
Lab results at the paint shop
神經毒劑被制成粉末狀
confirm the nerve toxin in powder form.
可通過空氣擴散
That's airborne deployment.
航空局應該禁飛所有飛機
The FAA should ground air traffic.
-我去辦  -謝謝你
- I'll make it happen. - Thank you.
照顧好你自己
Take care of yourself.
你們來得正好
Good. You're here.
尼爾森和詹姆森追查了你所看到的
Nelson and Jameson have been investigating the web streams
主謀屋里的樣子
you described seeing in our rider's room,
但尚未鎖定任何潛在嫌犯
but they haven't identified any potential targets.
不是那樣的
It wasn't like that.
看起來更像是觀賞世界景色的窗口
It was more like a collection of windows to the world.
還有件比較奇怪的事
There was something else that was odd.
他和我說話時一點都不緊張
He wasn't nervous talking to me.
反而更像是  好奇
He was more... curious.
如果如加布里爾所說  主謀重病纏身
If he's ill, as Gabriel says,
那他可能必須待在室內
it may be keeping him indoors.
我去看看有什么情報
I'm gonna take a look at the intel.
你和麗貝卡談得怎么樣
So, how did your visit with Rebecca go?
我嚴格遵守了規程  如果你是想問這個
I didn't break protocol, if that's what you're asking.
我知道你沒有  你循規蹈矩得很
I know you didn't. You're too stubborn for that.
盡管你腦子里裝了臺超級電腦
For a man with a supercomputer in his head,
但有時你真是笨得可以
you can be really stupid sometimes.
你以為我不想告訴她
Do you really think I don't want to tell her?
你以為我現在不是萬分糾結
You think it's not haunting me right now?
但想一想  這里還有千千萬萬的母親
But then I think -- how can I use my position
不能像我這樣保護自己女兒  我又怎么能
to reveal that kind of information, when there are
利用職權之便  向自己的女兒泄露機密信息
so many other mothers with daughters who can't?
因為你的女兒只此一人
Because none of them are your daughter.
告訴她實情不會讓你軟弱  莉莉安
Telling her doesn't make you weak, Lillian.
只會讓你更有人情味
It makes you human.
關鍵問題在于  毒劑到底跑哪去了
So, the question is, where the hell is the toxin?
在哪都有可能  現在根本不可能找到
It could be anywhere. It's impossible to find it now.
你想什么呢
What are you thinking?
我們漏掉了一環
There's a step missing.
是啊  現在就缺千萬平民在地上抽搐呻吟了
Yeah, the part where thousands of people writhe on the ground.
天啊  天啊  你哪來的心情開玩笑
My god! My god! How can you joke? Huh?!
加布里爾  莉莉安和萊利
Gabriel, Lillian, Riley -
-都不顧安危沖到前線  -我知道  老爸
- all out there. - I know they are, dad.
你知道我一緊張就愛開玩笑
You know I joke when I get nervous.
我們現在對付的人不僅
We are dealing with someone who is not only capable
想得出如此邪惡的犯罪計劃
of conceiving of such horror,
還有足夠的技術和資源去實現這一計劃
but who has the skills and the access to execute it.
我明白了
Okay.
你剛說漏了一環
You said we were missing a step?
沒錯
Yes.
簡易的武器系統有三個必須要素
An improvised weapons system has three necessary elements.
-殺傷性物質  -有了
- Materials. - Check.
-組裝工序  -也有了
- Manufacture. - Check.
以及部署方法
Deployment.
目前每一個要素都有專人分工負責
Each step so far has been totally compartmentalized.
他迫使一個人買來化學原料
He used one guy to purchase the chemicals,
再迫使另一人制出毒劑
another to cook,
兩個人唯一的聯系  就是黑客本人
and the only common thread -- the hacker himself.
那這位黑客現在在干什么
Well, what does the hacker do now?
黑電腦
He hacks.
他正在尋找第三個受迫者去部署毒劑
He's gonna hitch up a third mule to deploy the toxin.
漢娜  來吃早飯了
Hannah, breakfast.
再等一會兒
Just one more minute.
爸爸來看我  我跳舞呢
Daddy, watch me. I'm dancing.
等會就去  寶貝  我先付幾筆賬
I will, baby. I just got to pay a couple of bills first.
你今天不準上班  埃里克
你是誰
真正的問題是你是誰  埃里克
還是該叫你凱文·山德烈
你想怎樣
各位  我們正給你們發一個地址
Guys, we're sending an address to your GPS right now.
屬于一個受保護證人  名叫埃里克·漢森
It's for a witsec detainee named Eric Hanson.
他肯定就是下一個受迫者
He must be the next mule.
我們已要求法警找到
I ordered the U.S. Marshals to detain
舊金山市內所有受保護證人
all the active witsec protectees in San Francisco.
只有三個證人沒找到
They picked up all but three.
其中一個得了晚期白血病正在重癥監護室里
One has advanced leukemia and is in the ICU.
還有一個因為打老婆蹲了號子  真好
One is in jail for beating his wife -- lovely.
最后一個就是埃里克·漢森
And the third is this Eric Hanson.
是一個龐氏騙局的掛名負責人
He was the front man in a Ponzi scheme.
-為什么法警還沒抓著他  -讓我猜猜
- Why haven't the marshals picked him up? - Let me guess.
因為他已經走了
'Cause already gone.
沒有電話記錄  也沒人來過
There was no phone call. No one came to the house.
妻子說上一秒他還在付賬單
Wife says one minute he was paying bills.
下一秒就走了
The next, he just took off.
沒說去哪也沒說為什么
Didn't say where he was going or why.
我好奇的是
The thing I'm wondering is,
每一個受迫者都有特殊技能
each of these mules has had a special skill.
那漢森的是什么
What's Hanson's?
我還不知道
I don't know yet.
游戲機還開著  上面有攝像機
The video game is on. It has a camera.
也許能記下來發生的事
It might have recorded what happened.
我進來了
I'm in.
他們的女兒在跳舞
Their daughter was dancing.
我在解析他的電腦
I'm chipping his laptop.
你想干什么
去阿拉摩公園  等待下一步指令
阿拉摩公園
Alamo Park.
安東
Anton?
誰告訴你這個名字的
Who told you this name?
我不知道他是誰  但我想...
I don't know who he is, but I'm thinking
和告訴你在這兒等的是同一個人
it's the same guy who told you to be here.
你知道這是什么嗎
You understand what this is?
你知道該怎么做嗎
You understand what to do?
我知道你桌子下面藏了把槍
I know you have a gun under the table.
我也是
So do I.
歡迎回來
Welcome back.
現在  你的手機隨時會響  把它給我
Now, your phone is going to ring any second. Give it to me.
-我想和他對話  -什么
- I want to talk to him. - What?!
計劃有變
Change of plan.
安東  你也許能活下來
You might get to live after all, Anton.
有對男女朝你這邊來
There's a man and a woman about to head in your direction,
從南邊過來
coming from the south.
按我說的做
Do exactly as I say,
你還有機會能取回你的小命
and you stand a fighting chance of getting your life back.
加布里爾  你看  攝像機
Gabriel, look. The camera.
你死還是他死  安東  別讓他們過去
Kill or be killed, Anton. Don't let them pass!
-快跑  那邊  -你在說什么
- Run! That way! - What are you talking about?!
-做就行了  我會拖住他們  -拖住誰
- Just do it! I'll hold them off! - Hold who off?!
白癡  快跑啊
Idiot! Run!
公園周圍全是攝像機
Cameras all over the park.
我進來了
I'm in.
我看到安東了  他有把槍
I've got Anton. He has a gun.
-漢森在哪  -我還沒看見他
- Where's Hanson? - I don't see him yet.
該死  攝像機都關了
Damn it! The cameras just went down!
他知道我們在這兒
He knows we're here.
趴下
Get down!
疏散群眾  我來抓他
Get the people out. I got him.
快走  離開  快離開
Go! Move! Move!
趴下
Get down!
放下槍  聯邦特工  站住
Drop it! Federal agent! Stop!
他在哪  漢森在哪
Where is he?! Where's Hanson?!
是你嗎
Is that you?
我說你真是神通廣大
You are resourceful. I'll give you that.
誰把你變成這樣的
Who made you like this?
我不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you mean.
你很聰明  很有能力  很有多長處
You're smart. You have skills. You got a lot going for you.
為什么你想害人
Why do you want to hurt people?
你是這么想的  我有很多長處
Is that what you think? I have a lot going for me?
除了自卑
Except for feeling sorry for yourself.
你就想用這個試圖來打敗我
Is this the part where you attempt to antagonize me,
激怒我讓我暴露身份
irritate me to the point where I reveal myself to you?
我不需要你暴露自己
I don't need you to reveal yourself.
對我來說你們都是一種貨色
You're all the same to me.
你們支離破碎
You're broken,
你們覺得自己的所作所為是一種補救
and you think what you're doing's gonna fix it.
我才沒支離破碎  我對修東西毫無興趣
I'm not broken, and I'm not interested in fixing anything.
你在說謊
You're lying.
是嗎
Oh, am I?
你告訴我了
You have a tell.
你每次一說謊就啜吸管
You take a sip of that straw every time you lie to me.
不管你認為自己做的是什么
Well, whatever you think you're doing,
都不會成功的
it ain't gonna work.
已經成功了
It already has.
對我來說你們都是一種貨色
You're all the same to me.
你們支離破碎
You're broken,
你們覺得自己的所作所為是一種補救
and you think what you're doing's gonna fix it.
我才沒支離破碎  我對修東西毫無興趣
I'm not broken, and I'm not interested in fixing anything.
等等  這里  后面...
Wait. There it is, right after the, uh,
吸吸管的聲音  對
foghorn -- the straw. Yep.
加布里爾  你是對的
Gabriel, you're right.
吸東西的聲音很奇怪
That sucking sound is odd, though.
很用力
Deliberate.
像是虹吸管
It's like a siphon.
是種單向咬嘴閥  老天
It's a non-return bite valve. God!
一般用在為四肢癱瘓的人
Found on hands-free drinking systems
設計的免提飲水系統上
used by quadriplegics.
主謀是癱瘓者
Our rider is paralyzed.
這或許就解釋了為什么選這種毒
Which might explain the choice of toxin.
導致癱瘓  而非死亡
Paralysis, not death.
他想每個人都和他一樣
He wants everyone to be like him.
這樣一來范圍縮小了
That narrows the profile.
莉莉安  美國還有上百萬人
Well, Lillian, there are still millions of people
屬于這種殘疾
in the U.S. incapacitated in this way.
-他可能在任何地方  -各位  快想想
- He could be anywhere. - Come on, people! Think!
有個人手里掌握著大量的神經毒素啊
We've got a mule out there with a tank full of a neurotoxin!
找到他
Just find him!
好吧  聽著
All right, look.
我們知道這家伙掌握了瘋狂的高科技技能
We know that the guy's got mad tech skills, right?
最初打電話的時候
And in the first call,
他以為加布里爾當過運動員
he thought Gabriel was an athlete.
外行不是那么容易看出來的
It often takes one to know one.
所以他殘疾之前是個運動員
Okay, so he was an athlete before he was incapacitated,
并且他還是個科技專家
and he's a technology expert.
不錯  還能知道什么
That's good. So what else do we know?
不僅僅是科技的問題  而是他如何使用
It's not just the technology. It's how he uses it.
科技就好像是他本人的延伸
It's like an extension of himself.
這塊你比較了解
Something you know a little bit about.
他脅迫別人去做他們不愿意做的事情
He manipulates people to do things they wouldn't do
他肯定是抓住了這些人的弱點
unless he was pressing their buttons.
他在給他們"編程"
He's programming them,
這塊就是你比較了解了
something you might know a little bit about.
-不好意思  -加上這個背景
- Too shamed. - Add to that his environment.
他被電腦包圍著
He's surrounded by computers
那是他跟外界的聯系
that connect him to the outside world.
可它們無法"聯系"他  反而"孤立"了他
But they don't connect him, they isolate him.
你之前對我說什么來的  博士
What was it you said to me, doc?
芯片會逾越我作為人類的能力  但是
The chip will exceed my human abilities, but...
我們不能讓它逾越你的人性
We can't ever let it exceed your humanity.
他身邊可沒有人提醒他
He didn't have anyone around to remind him of that.
還有什么信息
All right, what else we got?
你好  我是麗貝卡  請留言
Hi. You've reached Rebecca. Please leave a message.
莉莉安
Lillian?
是我女兒
My daughter.
我們不常見面
We haven't always gotten along.
很不容易
It's not easy.
你很擔心她
And you're worried about her.
也許你應該放下規定  只做個媽媽
Maybe you should forget protocol, just be her mom.
我走不開的
I can't leave.
莉莉安
Lillian...
我十五歲的時候  對我媽媽的男朋友開了槍
I was 15 when I shot my mother's boyfriend.
她和我都明白  如果我沒有那么做
She and I both know that if I hadn't,
他會殺了她的
he would have killed her.
可我們還是十四年沒有聯系
And we still didn't speak for 14 years.
不論你們之間有什么障礙
Whatever there is between you two,
我知道你能解決的  相信我
I know you can fix it. Believe me.
可如果你不信任她  就無從談起了
But not if you don't trust her.
如果你不...  至少
Not if you don't... At least
給她個了解你的機會
give her a chance to really know you.
莉莉安  我們會找到那家伙的
Lillian, we will find this guy.
謝謝你  萊利
Thank you, Riley.
霧笛
Foghorn.
是霧笛
The foghorn!
霧笛怎么了
What about it?
尼爾森  播一下那段電話錄音
Nelson, bring up the recording of the call
-就在霧笛響起的時候  -好的
- right at the sound of the foghorn. - Yeah, you got it.
我沒毛病  也沒想修好什么
I'm not broken, and I'm not interested in fixing anything.
那個霧笛很有名
That foghorn is famous.
它就在金門橋的塔上
It's on the tower of the Golden Gate Bridge.
等等  你知道的  附近有什么標志物
Wait. You know this. What neighborhoods are near there?
奶牛低地  普西迪基地  碼頭
Uh, Cow Hollow, the Presidio, and the marina.
如果他癱瘓了
If he's paralyzed,
他肯定要有坡道或者電梯
he'd have built ramps or maybe an elevator.
建房子的話  是需要建筑許可的
And if it's a house, there'd be building permits.
我進入建筑檢驗系統了
I'm in the Building Inspector's system right now.
過去十年里  這里有
There were 623 permit requests
623個建造殘障坡道的許可請求
for handicap upgrades in the past 10 years.
都包含了完工的房屋照片
All include photos of the work being done.
鑒于他所作的一切
For the kind of processing he's doing,
這家伙肯定需要高速ISDN線路
this guy would need a high-speed ISDN line
至少T3級別
at least a T3.
好的  普通居民很少使用這種東西
Okay. That's rare for residential use.
范圍縮小到一個  喬納森·凱恩
That narrows it to one. Jonathan Cain.
加布里爾  你能連進T3線路嗎
Gabriel, can you access a T3 line?
我已經連進他的攝像頭了
I'm in his webcam now.
看到什么了
What do you see?
幕后的主謀
Our rider.
行動吧
Let's go.
我安排了兩人的組隊守在房子后面
I've got a two-man team positioned out back,
以防他逃跑
in case he runs.
他跑不了的
He's not running.
-什么事  -喬納森·凱恩在嗎
- Can I help you? - Is Jonathan Cain here?
喬納森  怎么了
Jonathan? Why?
這是怎么了
What on earth is going on?
我們是聯邦探員  他在嗎
We're Federal Agents. Is he here?
他當然在
Of course he's here.
他已經很多年沒離開過這房子了
He hasn't left the house in years.
聯邦探員  毒素在哪
Federal Agents. Where's the toxin?
太遲了
You're too late.
你好  請說一下姓名
Hi. Name, please?
埃里克·漢森
Eric Hanson.
歡迎來到年度股東大會  漢森先生
Welcome to the annual shareholders meeting, Mr. Hanson.
大會馬上開始
We'll be starting in just a few minutes.
現在就可以進去了
If you like, you can head right on in.
漢森在哪  你想在哪兒釋放毒氣
Where's Hanson? Where's the toxin gonna be released?
在貢獻最大的地方
Where it will do the most good.
貢獻  你會毀掉很多人
Good? People's lives are gonna be destroyed.
喬納森  發生了什么事  這是怎么了
Jonathan? What's happening? What's going on?
你丈夫打算在舊金山市的某個地方
Your husband is about to release a deadly neurotoxin
釋放致死性的神經毒素
somewhere in San Francisco.
-什么  -重點是  毒素不會致死
- What? - The agent isn't deadly. That's the whole point.
我的老天  你到底做了什么
For God's sake, what have you done?
這場賽跑是
The race was the first time
你第一次發現身體有異樣是嗎
You realized something was wrong, wasn't it?
這一切都是因此而起
That's what this is all about.
以前我在一所大學的化學試驗室工作
I was working in the chem lab at the college.
出了一起事故
There was an accident.
他們說我得了美尼爾氏綜合癥
They said it was meniere's ataxia,
但我沒有絕望  治愈并不遙遠
But I shouldn't despair, that a cure wasn't that far off.
可到現在  我甚至無法抱緊我的妻子
Now...I can't even hold my own wife.
喬納森  喬納森  聽我說
Jonathan. Jonathan, listen to me.
我愛你  其他的都無所謂
Nothing matters, except that I love you.
你不明白
You don't understand.
你感到孤單  與世隔絕
You feel isolated, alone.
越想透過網絡與外界聯系
The more you try to connect with the world
越讓你變得孤立無援
through all these wires, the more isolated you become.
越是依賴科技
And the more dependent you become on the technology,
就會越發失去自我
the more you feel you're losing yourself.
你試圖說服自己不是一臺機器
You try to convince yourself you're not a machine,
可別人卻一直這樣看待你
but that's the way everyone else looks at you.
但你還是打電話給我了
But you called me.
依然試圖與他人保持聯系
You were trying to connect.
你還有挽回的余地
You can still stop this,
-喬納森  -這就是你的最佳演技了嗎
- Jonathan. - Is that your best carnival act?
你看了看墻上的一張照片
You look at a photo on the wall,
就以為自己能說動我了嗎
and think you know how to get to me?
我想當你看著那張照片時
I think you look at the photo on the wall,
你是多么希望當年那個他能夠回來
and you want that man back so badly you're willing
用他從未想過的方式替你向世界宣泄
to rage against the world in ways that man never imagined.
把他帶走
Get him out of here.
嗨  媽媽
Hi, mom.
麗貝卡  我要你馬上出城
Rebecca, I need you to leave town
去馬林縣跟你爸爸過個周末
and go spend the weekend up in Marin with your father.
你在說些什么
What are you talking about?
趕緊收拾東西  現在就去
Just get your things together and go, please.
我哪都不去  你為什么要這樣
I'm not going anywhere. What's this about?
老天爺  你用腦子想想我為什么會來這
For god's sake, use your brain. Why am I here, Rebecca?
因為你是個控制狂  從來都不尊重我
Because you're a control freak, you have no respect for me,
以為包括家人在內的
and you somehow think that everyone,
所有人  都是你的手下
including your own family, works for you.
這個場面和我預想的大不相同
This isn't going the way I wanted it to go.
那你覺得你這樣
Well, how did you think it would go
硬闖進來大聲命令我  我該作何反應
when you just barge in here and start shouting orders?
你說的的確有道理
That's a very good point.
真的嗎
It is?
確實如此
Yes, it is.
麗貝卡  我求你別問問題
Rebecca, I need you to not ask me any questions
趕緊去你爸爸那
and just go to your father's house.
晚點我會打電話跟你解釋
I'll call later and explain.
拜托了  寶貝
Please, honey.
就聽我這一次
Just do this for me this once.
好吧  媽  我這就走
Okay, mom. I'll leave right now.
謝謝
Thank you.
聽著  凱恩必須馬上釋放毒氣
Look, guys, Cain needs to deploy the toxin soon
否則就會失效
before it becomes useless.
使人麻痹究竟有什么用
What good can come from paralyzing other people?
能幫助他恢復嗎
How does that help him recover?
-他只想讓別人都和他一樣  -沒錯
- 'Cause it makes them just like him. - Yes.
這就是醫療發展的悲哀現狀
That's -- that is the sad truth of medical discovery --
得某種病的人越多
The more people suffering from a disease or a condition,
刺激對應治療方式的動力就越大
the more incentive there is to develop a cure --
這個動力就是錢
The incentive being money.
尼爾森  有人在開發美尼爾病的治療方法嗎
Nelson, is anyone developing a treatment for meniere's ataxia?
沒有
No one.
詹寧斯制藥公司呢
What about Jennings Pharmaceutical?
他們確實在做  但研發費用過于高昂
Yeah, they were in it, but R&D got too expensive,
他們九個月前停止了為期五年的試驗
so they pulled out of a five-year trial nine months ago.
這就對了  這是凱恩最后的機會
Yes, this would have been Cain's last chance.
漢森就是股東之一
Hanson's a shareholder.
詹寧斯公告今天將在舊金山召開
Jennings is having their annual shareholders meeting
年度股東會議
today in San Francisco.
所有董事會成員都會出席
The entire board will be there.
與去年同期相比
And the price-to-earnings ratio
公司的本益比顯著提高了11%
is up a sharp 11% from this time last year,
這大部分得益于血管診斷學等
largely due to inroads into a new tech,
新技術的獲得和治療類市場
vascular diagnostics, and treatment market.
今年我們將在這部分分配33%
Now, we cap out here at 33%.
所有人聽著
Listen up!
所有人  撤離這間劇院
Everybody needs to evacuate this theater.
抱歉  發生了什么事
Excuse me. What's going on?
不要攜帶隨身物品
Leave your personal belongings where they are
跟隨警官撤離
and follow the officers outside.
立刻
Do it now!
發現他了
Got him.
站住
Stop!
-我的家人  對不起  我  -在哪兒
- My family. I'm sorry. I -- - Where is it?!
他會殺了我妻子和女兒的
He was gonna kill my wife and my little girl!
我們抓到他了  他傷害不了他們
We have him! He can't hurt them!
快說  在哪里
Now, where the hell is it?!
我的天吶  在我座位下面
Oh, my God. I-it's under my seat!
在箱子里  是個定時炸彈
It's in the case! And it's on a timer!
-還有多久  -我不知道  幾分鐘吧
- How much time is left? - I don't know -- a couple minutes.
找到了
I got it.
-還有多久  -1分33  32
- How much time? - A minute 33, 32...
-卡西迪  你聽到了嗎  -我們都聽到了
- Cassidy, you copy? - We're with you.
這點時間不夠疏散所有人員
There's not enough time for a full evacuation.
如果這種神經性毒素釋放
If this nerve toxin is released,
會滲入整棟大樓的通風系統
it could seep into the building's vents.
會污染整棟大樓的周邊環境
It could contaminate the entire area surrounding the building.
21 20  -二氧化碳
21, 20. - CO2!
你需要二氧化碳  加布里爾
You need CO2, Gabriel!
-附近有滅火器嗎  -有
- Is there a fire extinguisher nearby? - Yeah.
二氧化碳會怎么樣  會解除毒素嗎
CO2 will what, neutralize it?
不  二氧化碳會凍結計時器的振蕩器
No, CO2 will freeze the timer's oscillator.
-會給你爭取點時間  -有多久
- It'll buy you some time. - For how long?
-未知  -未知
- Unknown. - Unknown?!
好極了  噴吧
Great. Hit it.
我看不到計時器
I can't see the timer.
這無所謂  加布里爾
Yeah, it doesn't matter, Gabriel!
-現在你需要高溫  -高溫
- Now you need an intense heat. - Intense heat?!
現在你要我在人群密集的大樓里
Now you want me to blow up a chemical weapon
炸毀化學武器嗎
inside a crowded building?
是  最好在二十秒左右之內
Yeah, preferably in the next 20 seconds or so.
大廈鍋爐房
The building furnace.
這邊走
This way.
向毒罐增加熱量
Adding heat to the pressurized cannisters
會導致爆炸
will result in an explosion.
是  但那應該會起到催化
Yes, but that should -- should catalyze a reaction
火藥和空氣中的氮的發生反應
between the powder and the nitrogen in the air
使毒素失效
and render the toxin inert.
應該  你好像沒信心啊  博士
Should? You don't sound too confident, Doc.
-老爸  -賭一把吧
- Dad? - Crapshoot.
好極了
That's great.
-準備好了嗎  -來吧
- Are you ready? - Do it!
快走
Move!
萊利
Riley?
加布里爾呢
Where's Gabriel?
他沒事
He's fine.
你和你女兒之間怎么樣了
How did things go with your daughter?
很高興我去找了她
I'm glad I went.
我也是
Me too.
我以為  她長大了就會好一些
I thought it would, uh, get easier as she grew older.
但就算我知道我做的是對的
But even when I know I'm doing the right thing,
也從未感覺對過
it just never feels right.
能多說一句嗎
Can I speak freely?
從沒限制過你啊
Were you not speaking freely before?
關于我媽媽的很多事情
There are so many things about my mom
我希望她有勇氣告訴我
I wish she'd had the courage to tell me.
莉莉安  如果麗貝卡了解你
Lillian, if Rebecca knew you --
真正的了解你
I mean really knew you --
她會非常驕傲的
She'd be so proud.
我本想帶你去外面吃飯的
You know, I would have taken you to dinner.
那你就會錯過我手藝了
But then you would have missed my cooking.
誰教你做菜的
Who taught you to cook?
他一直煮了一手好菜
He always was a good cook.
他甚至為你的寶貝親手做飯
I mean, he even made your baby food himself.
是的  每當他生我氣時
Yeah. He usually reminds me of that
他經常會提醒我
when he's mad at me.
你畫完了嗎
So, did you finish your paintings?
除了一張之外  你要看看嗎
Um...All but one. Do you want to see it?
如果你不介意  我當然要看
Sure, if you don't mind.
過來這里
Come on.
麗貝卡
Oh, Rebecca.
記得嗎
Do you remember?
當然記得  寶貝
Of course, sweetheart.
我當然記得
Of course. I remember.
我記得那天的每分每秒
I remember every second of it.
親愛的  我知道經常令你很難受
Oh, honey, I-I know it's often been hard for you.
你總是覺得從未真正了解過你的媽媽
You've always felt that you never really know your mother.
我認為現在是時候改變了
Well, I think it's time to change that.